A Guide to the JDR 3rd Fund records FA081
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files, 1967-1979; 11; 88 Cubic Feet 204 document cases
  - Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files - Project Files, 11.B
    - Project IMPACT - Reports - Progress, 1972 (Box 183, Folder 1392)
    - Project IMPACT - Reports - Progress, 1972 (Box 183, Folder 1393)
    - Project IMPACT - Report - Steering Committee Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 183, Folder 1394)
    - Project IMPACT - Reports - Final, 1973 (Box 183, Folder 1395)
    - Project IMPACT - Reports - Final, 1973 (Box 183, Folder 1396)
    - Project IMPACT - Reports - Final, 1973 (Box 183, Folder 1397)
    - Project IMPACT - Reports - Summary, 1973 (Box 183, Folder 1398)
    - Project IMPACT - Wenner, Gene C. - "The Story of IMPACT: A Coordinator's View", 1976 (Box 183, Folder 1399)
    - Project IMPACT - Music Educator's National Conference, 1971-1973 (Box 184, Folder 1400)
    - Project IMPACT - National Endowment for the Arts, 1973 (Box 184, Folder 1401)
    - Project IMPACT - Pennsylvania State Evaluation Team - Report, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 1402)
    - Project IMPACT - Pennsylvania State Evaluation Team - Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 184, Folder 1403)
    - Project IMPACT - Steering Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 184, Folder 1404)
    - Project IMPACT - United States Office of Education, 1970-1973 (Box 184, Folder 1405)
    - Project IMPACT - Miscellany - Statement by Grace Stanistreet, 1971 (Box 184, Folder 1406)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Grant File, 1971 (Box 184, Folder 1407)
      Grant # B-7211-E, #EX-72121-E, #EC-72121-E, #B-7369-E, #B-73109-E, #B-7466-E, #B-7534-E, #B-7575-E
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Grant File, 1971 (Box 185, Folder 1408)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Grant File, 1971 (Box 185, Folder 1409)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 185, Folder 1410)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 185, Folder 1411)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 185, Folder 1412)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 185, Folder 1413)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 186, Folder 1414)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Reports - Planning, 1971-1973 (Box 186, Folder 1415)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Reports - Evaluation, 1971-1975 (Box 186, Folder 1416)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Reports - Quarterly, 1971-1974 (Box 186, Folder 1417)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Reports - Quarterly, 1971-1974 (Box 186, Folder 1418)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Reports - Quarterly, 1974-1976 (Box 187, Folder 1419)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Reports - Quarterly, 1974-1976 (Box 187, Folder 1420)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Evaluation - Jean Chen, 1974-1975 (Box 187, Folder 1421)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Evaluation - Jean Chen, 1974-1975 (Box 187, Folder 1422)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Evaluation - Jean Chen, 1974-1975 (Box 187, Folder 1423)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Evaluation Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 187, Folder 1424)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Evaluation Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 188, Folder 1425)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Evaluation Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 188, Folder 1426)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Meetings, 1971-1976 (Box 188, Folder 1427)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Meetings, 1971-1976 (Box 188, Folder 1428)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Miscellany, 1970-1975 (Box 188, Folder 1429)
    - Jefferson County Public Schools - Brochures, 1973-1976 (Box 188, Folder 1430)
    - John Adams High School - Proposal File, 1970; 1973 (Box 189, Folder 1431)
      Grant #B-7190-E, #B-71109-E, #B-72110-E
    - John Adams High School - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 189, Folder 1432)
    - John Adams High School - Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 189, Folder 1433)
    - John Adams High School - Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 189, Folder 1434)
    - John Adams High School - Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 189, Folder 1435)
    - John Adams High School - Project Image - Materials, 1971-1972 (Box 189, Folder 1436)
    - John Adams High School - Brochures, 1970-1973 (Box 190, Folder 1437)
    - Lane County Public Schools - Project File, 1970-1974 (Box 190, Folder 1438)
      Grant #B-70114-E, #B-71110-E
    - Lane County Public Schools - Project File, 1970-1974 (Box 190, Folder 1439)
    - Lane County Public Schools - Project File, 1970-1974 (Box 190, Folder 1440)
    - Lane County Public Schools - Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 190, Folder 1441)
    - Lane County Public Schools - Visit, 1970 (Box 190, Folder 1442)
    - Lane County Public Schools - Brochures, 1968-1969 (Box 190, Folder 1443)
    - Lane County Public Schools - Brochures, 1969-1973 (Box 191, Folder 1444)
    - League of Cities - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 191, Folder 1445)
    - League of Cities - Meetings, January-June 1976 (Box 191, Folder 1446)
    - League of Cities - Meetings, January-June 1976 (Box 191, Folder 1447)
    - League of Cities - Meetings, January-June 1976 (Box 191, Folder 1448)
    - League of Cities - Meetings, July 1976-1979 (Box 192, Folder 1449)
    - League of Cities - Meetings, July 1976-1979 (Box 192, Folder 1450)
    - League of Cities - Meetings, July 1976-1979 (Box 192, Folder 1451)
    - League of Cities - Meetings - Payment File, 1976-1978 (Box 192, Folder 1452)
    - League of Cities - Hartford, 1978 (Box 192, Folder 1453)
    - League of Cities - Little Rock, 1975-1979 (Box 192, Folder 1454)
    - League of Cities - Minneapolis, 1973-1978 (Box 192, Folder 1455)
    - League of Cities - New York City - Board of Education, 1974-1979 (Box 193, Folder 1456)
    - League of Cities - New York City - Board of Education, 1974-1979 (Box 193, Folder 1457)
    - League of Cities - New York City - Learning Cooperative - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 193, Folder 1458)
    - League of Cities - New York City - Learning Cooperative - Meetings, 1973 (Box 193, Folder 1459)
    - League of Cities - New York City - Lincoln Center Institute, 1972-1978 (Box 193, Folder 1460)
    - League of Cities - New York City - Miscellany, 1969-1979 (Box 193, Folder 1461)
    - League of Cities - Seattle - Arts Commission, 1973 (Box 194, Folder 1462)
    - League of Cities - Seattle - Junior League, 1973-1975 (Box 194, Folder 1463)
    - League of Cities - Seattle - Public Schools, 1974-1978 (Box 194, Folder 1464)
    - League of Cities - Seattle - Public Schools, 1974-1978 (Box 194, Folder 1465)
    - League of Cities - Seattle - Public Schools, 1974-1978 (Box 194, Folder 1466)
    - League of Cities - Seattle - Visits, 1974-1978 (Box 194, Folder 1467)
    - League of Cities - Seattle - Visits, 1974-1978 (Box 194, Folder 1468)
    - League of Cities - Seattle - Visits, 1974-1978 (Box 194, Folder 1469)
    - League of Cities - Seattle - Brochures, 1975-1979 (Box 195, Folder 1470)
    - League of Cities - Seattle - Miscellany - Poets in Residence Program, 1973-1974 (Box 195, Folder 1471)
    - League of Cities - Seattle - Miscellany - Poets in Residence Program, 1973-1974 (Box 195, Folder 1472)
    - League of Cities - Winston-Salem, 1973-1979 (Box 195, Folder 1473)
    - League of Cities - Jane Remer - "The League of Cities for the Arts in Education", 1977 (Box 195, Folder 1474)
    - Metropolitan Cultural Alliance - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 195, Folder 1475)
      Grant #B-7470-E
    - Metropolitan Cultural Alliance - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 195, Folder 1476)
    - Metropolitan Cultural Alliance - Reports, 1974 (Box 196, Folder 1477)
    - Metropolitan Cultural Alliance - Reports, 1974 (Box 196, Folder 1478)
    - Metropolitan Cultural Alliance - Visit, April 14-15, 1975 (Box 196, Folder 1479)
    - Metropolitan Cultural Alliance - Brochures, 1973-1974 (Box 196, Folder 1480)
    - Metropolitan Cultural Alliance - Miscellany, 1974 (Box 196, Folder 1481)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Project Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 196, Folder 1482)
      Grants #B-6976-E, #B72109-E, #B-7368-E
    - Mineola Public Schools - Project Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 197, Folder 1483)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Project Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 197, Folder 1484)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Project Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 197, Folder 1485)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Working Papers, 1969 (Box 197, Folder 1486)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Reports, Progress, October 1969-June 1971 (Box 197, Folder 1487)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Reports, Progress, October 1969-June 1971 (Box 197, Folder 1488)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Reports, Progress, August 1971-March 1973 (Box 198, Folder 1489)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Report - Draft I, 1969-1973 (Box 198, Folder 1490)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Report - Draft II, 1969-1973 (Box 198, Folder 1491)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Report - Draft II, 1969-1973 (Box 198, Folder 1492)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Report - Draft II, 1969-1973 (Box 198, Folder 1493)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Report - Draft III, 1969-1973 (Box 198, Folder 1494)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Report - Draft III, 1969-1973 (Box 198, Folder 1495)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Report - Draft III, 1969-1973 (Box 198, Folder 1496)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Report - Draft IV, 1969-1973 (Box 199, Folder 1497)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Report - Draft V (Final), 1969-1973 (Box 199, Folder 1498)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Report - Draft V (Final), 1969-1973 (Box 199, Folder 1499)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Meetings, 1969-1975 (Box 199, Folder 1500)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Arts Events Program - Materials, 1970-1972 (Box 199, Folder 1501)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Arts Events Program - Brochures, 1970-1971 (Box 199, Folder 1502)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Arts Events Program - Brochures, 1971-1974 (Box 200, Folder 1503)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Brochures, 1967-1977 (Box 200, Folder 1504)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - "Artworlds" (Box 200, Folder 1505)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - "Artworlds" (Box 200, Folder 1506)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - "Creative Movement" (Box 200, Folder 1507)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - "Creative Movement" (Box 200, Folder 1508)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - "Man the Symbol Maker" (Box 201, Folder 1509)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - "Man the Symbol Maker" (Box 201, Folder 1510)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - "Mime as Non-Verbal Communication" (Box 201, Folder 1511)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - "Mime as Non-Verbal Communication" (Box 201, Folder 1512)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - "Ways of Knowing" (Box 201, Folder 1513)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - "Ways of Knowing" (Box 201, Folder 1514)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - Cards, Series I (Box 202, Folder 1514A)
    - Mineola Public Schools - Curriculum Materials - Cards, Series I and II (Box 203, Folder 1514B)
    - Museum of Modern Art - Children's Art Caravan - Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 204, Folder 1515)
      Grant #B-6868-E, #B-7191-E
    - Museum of Modern Art - Children's Art Caravan - Reports, 1970 (Box 204, Folder 1516)
    - Museum of Modern Art - Children's Art Caravan - Brochures, 1972 (Box 204, Folder 1517)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education (NASBE) - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 204, Folder 1518)
      Grant #B-7874-E
    - National Association of State Boards of Education (NASBE) - Survey, 1978 (Box 204, Folder 1519)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education (NASBE) - Survey, 1978 (Box 204, Folder 1520)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education (NASBE) - Survey, 1978 (Box 204, Folder 1521)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Project File, 1968-1973 (Box 204, Folder 1522)
      Grant #B-72112-E, #B-7371-E, #B-73105-E, #B-7465-E, #B-7547-E, #B-7647-E
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Project File, 1968-1973 (Box 204, Folder 1523)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Project File, 1974-1977 (Box 205, Folder 1524)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Project File, 1974-1977 (Box 205, Folder 1525)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Project File, 1974-1977 (Box 205, Folder 1526)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Project File, 1974-1977 (Box 205, Folder 1527)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Reports, 1972-1976 (Box 205, Folder 1528)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Reports, 1972-1976 (Box 205, Folder 1529)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Reports, 1972-1976 (Box 205, Folder 1530)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Meetings, May 1972-June 1973 (Box 206, Folder 1531)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Meetings, May 1972-June 1973 (Box 206, Folder 1532)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Meetings, May 1972-June 1973 (Box 206, Folder 1533)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Meetings, May 1972-June 1973 (Box 206, Folder 1534)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Meetings, May 1972-June 1973 (Box 206, Folder 1535)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Meetings, May 1972-June 1973 (Box 206, Folder 1536)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Meetings, July 1973-May 1975 (Box 207, Folder 1537)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Meetings, July 1973-May 1975 (Box 207, Folder 1538)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Meetings, July 1973-May 1975 (Box 207, Folder 1539)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Meetings, July 1973-May 1975 (Box 207, Folder 1540)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Meetings, July 1973-May 1975 (Box 207, Folder 1541)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Fonda-Fultonville District, 1972-1973 (Box 208, Folder 1542)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Fredonia District, 1972-1974 (Box 208, Folder 1543)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Greece District, 1972-1974 (Box 208, Folder 1544)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Millbrook District, 1972-1974 (Box 208, Folder 1545)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Monroe District, 1972 (Box 208, Folder 1546)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - New Hartford District, 1974 (Box 208, Folder 1547)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Utica District, 1972-1977 (Box 208, Folder 1548)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Utica District, 1972-1977 (Box 208, Folder 1549)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Miscellany - Brochures, 1974-1976 (Box 209, Folder 1550)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Miscellany - Brochures, 1974-1976 (Box 209, Folder 1551)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Miscellany (C-Z) (Box 209, Folder 1552)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Miscellany (C-Z) (Box 209, Folder 1553)
    - New York State Board of Education - Project SEARCH - Miscellany (C-Z) (Box 209, Folder 1554)
    - New York City - PS 3-M - Project File, 1971-1975 (Box 210, Folder 1555)
      Grant #B-7275-E, #B-7370-E
    - New York City - PS 3-M - Project File, 1971-1975 (Box 210, Folder 1556)
    - New York City - PS 3-M - Report, June 1972 (Box 210, Folder 1557)
    - New York City - PS 3-M - Report (Final), 1972-1973 (Box 210, Folder 1558)
    - New York City - PS 3-M - Brochures, 1971-1972 (Box 210, Folder 1559)
    - New York City - PS 51 - Reports, 1969 (Box 210, Folder 1560)
    - New York City - PS 51 - Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 211, Folder 1561)
    - New York City - PS 51 - Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 211, Folder 1562)
    - New York University - Project File, 1969-1970 (Box 211, Folder 1563)
      Grant #B-7075-E
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Project File, 1971-1979 (Box 211, Folder 1564)
      Grant #B-7291-E, #B-7373-E, #B-73107-E, #B-7467-E, #B7533-E, #B-7630-E
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Project File, 1971-1979 (Box 211, Folder 1565)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Project File, 1971-1979 (Box 211, Folder 1566)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Project File, 1971-1979 (Box 211, Folder 1567)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Reports - Arts in Education Program, 1971-1973 (Box 212, Folder 1568)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Reports - Arts in Education Program, 1971-1973 (Box 212, Folder 1569)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Reports - Arts in Education Program, 1971-1973 (Box 212, Folder 1570)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Meetings, 1971 (Box 212, Folder 1571)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Meetings, 1972-1975 (Box 213, Folder 1572)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Meetings, 1972-1975 (Box 213, Folder 1573)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Meetings, 1972-1975 (Box 213, Folder 1574)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Brochures (Box 213, Folder 1575)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Creative Education - Proposal, 1972 (Box 213, Folder 1576)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Creative Education - Packet, 1972 (Box 214, Folder 1577)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Creative Learning Program, 1973 (Box 214, Folder 1578)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Eye-Magic Theatre, 1972 (Box 214, Folder 1579)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Governor's Art Award, 1976 (Box 214, Folder 1580)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Council - Opening Doors Program, 1972-1977 (Box 214, Folder 1581)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Symposium - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 214, Folder 1582)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Symposium - Payment File, 1976-1978 (Box 214, Folder 1583)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Symposium - Reports, 1976 (Box 214, Folder 1584)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Symposium - Conference Materials, 1976 (Box 215, Folder 1585)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Symposium - Conference Materials, 1976 (Box 215, Folder 1586)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Symposium - Conference Materials, 1976 (Box 215, Folder 1587)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Symposium - Conference Packet, 1976 (Box 215, Folder 1588)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Symposium - Handbook, 1977 (Box 216, Folder 1589)
    - Oklahoma City Arts Symposium - Handbook - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 216, Folder 1590)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Project File, 1971-1979 (Box 216, Folder 1591)
      Grant #B-72111-E, #B-73104-E, #B-7548-E
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Project File, 1971-1979 (Box 216, Folder 1592)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Project File, 1971-1979 (Box 216, Folder 1593)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Project File, 1971-1979 (Box 216, Folder 1594)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Report, 1974-1976 (Box 216, Folder 1595)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Report, 1974-1976 (Box 217, Folder 1596)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 217, Folder 1597)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 217, Folder 1598)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 217, Folder 1599)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 217, Folder 1600)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 217, Folder 1601)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 218, Folder 1602)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 218, Folder 1603)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Memoranda, 1972-1979 (Box 218, Folder 1604)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Brochures, 1973-1979 (Box 218, Folder 1605)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Brochures, 1973-1979 (Box 218, Folder 1606)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Brochures, 1973-1979 (Box 218, Folder 1607)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany - "Aesthetic Education Program", 1973 (Box 219, Folder 1608)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany - "Aesthetics in Photography", 1973 (Box 219, Folder 1609)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany - "The Arts File", 1973-1977 (Box 219, Folder 1610)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany - "Arts in Basic Education", 1972-1974 (Box 219, Folder 1611)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany - "Arts in Education Academy", 1973 (Box 219, Folder 1612)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany (A-C) (Box 219, Folder 1613)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany - "Curriculum Guidelines Working Papers", 1973-1974 (Box 219, Folder 1614)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany - "Curriculum Guidelines--Packet", 1974 (Box 220, Folder 1615)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany - "Curriculum Guidelines--Packet", 1974 (Box 220, Folder 1616)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany - "Educational Quality Assessment", 1970-1971 (Box 220, Folder 1617)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany (F-T) (Box 220, Folder 1618)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany (F-T) (Box 220, Folder 1619)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany (F-T) (Box 220, Folder 1620)
    - Pennsylvania State Department of Education - Miscellany - "Ways and Meaning Place", 1975-1978 (Box 221, Folder 1621)
    - Pilot Projects - Summary Report, 1977 (Box 221, Folder 1622)
    - Pilot Projects - Central School District #2W (Ellenville, New York), 1966-1967 (Box 221, Folder 1623)
    - Pilot Projects - Education in the Arts, 1966-1968 (Box 221, Folder 1624)
    - Pilot Projects - Evanston Township (Illinois) High School, 1967 (Box 221, Folder 1625)
    - Pilot Projects - Flint (Michigan) Public Schools, 1967 (Box 221, Folder 1626)
    - Pilot Projects - Kettering Foundation - Institute for Development of Educational Activities (IDEA), 1966-1968 (Box 221, Folder 1627)
    - Pilot Projects - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities - Morgan Summer Project, 1966-1967 (Box 221, Folder 1628)
    - Pilot Projects - Robertson Center for the Arts and Sciences, 1966-1968 (Box 222, Folder 1629)
    - Pilot Projects - University of New Mexico, 1967-1968 (Box 222, Folder 1630)
    - Pilot Projects - University of New Mexico, 1967-1968 (Box 222, Folder 1631)
    - Pilot Projects - Waldrop, Gideon, 1966 (Box 222, Folder 1632)
    - Pilot Projects - Publications, 1964-1968 (Box 222, Folder 1633)
    - Ridge Street School - Project File, 1969 (Box 222, Folder 1634)
      Grant #B-69100-E, #B-7130-E, #B-71111-E
    - Ridge Street School - Project File, 1970-1973 (Box 223, Folder 1635)
    - Ridge Street School - Project File, 1970-1973 (Box 223, Folder 1636)
    - Ridge Street School - Project File, 1970-1973 (Box 223, Folder 1637)
    - Ridge Street School - Reports, 1969-1972 (Box 223, Folder 1638)
    - Ridge Street School - Reports, 1969-1972 (Box 223, Folder 1639)
    - Ridge Street School - Reports, 1969-1972 (Box 223, Folder 1640)
    - Ridge Street School - Miscellany - Brochures, 1969-1977 (Box 224, Folder 1641)
    - Ridge Street School - Miscellany - Handbook, 1968 (Box 224, Folder 1642)